connectwithlife.com 2008-01-01

# Connect With Life Home

|  |   |  |   
 |   
|  Homes |  |  Autos |  |  Mortgage |  |  Insurance |  Are you a [Real Estate Agent? ](http://www.replyrealestate.com/) or a [Car Dealer?](http://www.imotors.com/) |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |   
---|---  
| 

|   
---  
  
Reply, Inc. (“Reply”), which owns and operates ConnectWithLife.com (“Site"), understands that privacy concerns are extremely important to our customers. We are committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information and for that reason Reply has created this Privacy Policy.

**Acceptance of the Privacy Policy**  
By using Site and providing us with your information, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Site.

We may occasionally update the Privacy Policy as necessary to protect our customers, to reflect our current practices, and to comply with the changing legal requirements. We recommend that you check the Privacy Policy when you visit to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. All material changes to the Privacy Policy will be prominently posted at the time of the change. Your continued use of the Site means you accept those changes for all information you have provided to us.

**Policy Coverage**   
This policy covers how this Site treats personal information that the Site collects and receives from you, including information related to your use of the Site's products and services. Personal information is information you provide about yourself that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, and phone number. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or the content of websites of companies that the Site links to but does not own or control. In those cases in which you link to content provided by a third-party company, you will become subject to the security and privacy policies of those companies and the policies that are posted on the associated website. If you wish to restrict the disclosure of your personal information by those companies, you will have to direct any opt-out or other non-disclosure request to those companies in accordance with their respective policies. 

**Collection of Information**  
In order to service its customers, the Site collects personal information from consumers through request forms, surveys, and/or site registrations. The Site's request forms may require users to provide information, which may include but not be limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and certain financial and credit-related information. This information allows the Site to serve you, and to the extent you request service beyond that which the Site can provide, to match you with a service provider – such as real estate professional or automotive dealer – that can help address your specific request. This information also helps the Site in the development or referral of valued products and services offered by the Site and other companies that we believe will meet the continuing needs of our customers. The collected personal information is used primarily to route your request to the appropriate service provider and to allow Site and selected third-party companies to contact users for marketing purposes in the future. 

The Site may also record information on our server logs, including but not limited to your IP address, the Site cookie information, previous page visited, and the page you request. The Site uses information for the following general purposes: to customize content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, maintain or improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Sharing of your information**  
When you request services beyond those directly available from Site, we provide your personal information to selected service providers, such as real estate professionals or automotive dealers, who we believe can provide the product or service your request. The service provider may use your personal information to respond to your requests for information or provide further information about products and services that they believe will meet your continuing needs. As the service provider may keep and use your information whether or not you purchase their products or use their services, your personal information will be subject to their privacy policies, and you should contact them directly for more information about their specific privacy and opt-out policies.

The Site may provide personal information to other third-party companies that it believes will be able to provide you with valuable products, services, or other information that may be of interest. As such third parties may keep and use your information whether or not you purchase their products or use their services, your personal information will be subject to their privacy policies, and you should contact them directly for more information about their specific privacy and opt-out policies.

The Site responds to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Where we believe it is necessary, we will share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities or as otherwise required by law.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web server may transfer to your computer through your web browser. When this information is stored on your computer, our system is able to recognize your browser and in turn customize web page content for you. By using cookies, the Site is able to offer you the advantage of personalization that improves your experience. We will not use any cookies to retrieve other data from your hard drive or obtain sensitive information about you. Only the Site can access the cookies that we set. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain of our online services or website features. 

**Usage by Minors**  
Although the Site is intended for the use of adults, the forms on the Site are capable of collecting online contact information from children under the age of 13 who furnish it without prior parental consent. If you are under 13 years old, you should not register with or otherwise provide personal information to the Site.

**Security**  
The Site is regularly monitored for fraud, abuse, and unauthorized use of information to help protect your personal information that is under our control. 

**Do Not Call Registry Compliance**  
By submitting personal information to Site, you hereby grant written permission to Site, its service providers and selected third-party companies to contact you by telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. By providing personal information to Site, you thereby waive your right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in reference to these calls or contacts. 

**Opt-Out Opportunity**  
Site customers may opt-out of receiving further communications from Site at any time by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in any Site e-mail received by customer. Please note that unsubscribing from one email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other email list that you may be on. Please read the email carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from.

**Assignment**  
In its sole discretion, Site may transfer, sell or assign your personal information collected on and through the Site to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of Reply, Inc. 

*This Privacy Policy was made effective on December 13, 2007.   
  
|  |  |  |  Homes For Sale   
---|---  
  |  Price Range  
|   to  |     
|  Type   
|   
| Beds                        Baths |   
|                   |   
|  Location  
|   
|   
|  |  Instant Home Valuation   
---|---  
|  Street Address  
|   
|   
|   
  
| |   New Car Price Quote   
---|---  
| Select A Vehicle  
|   
|   
|   
|
